comeonaussie.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy for Come On Aussie Internet Services : Come On Aussie

The privacy of our visitors to all sites managed by Come On Aussie Internet Services is important to us.

Here is information on the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit sites belonging to Come On Aussie Internet Services, and how we safeguard your information.

Please note that we will **NEVER** sell, rent or lend out your personal information to third parties.

If you are contacted by telephone by someone who says they are a representative of Come On Aussie, please be assured that it is NOT us as we do NOT use telemarketing services.

**Log Files**

As with all websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Since log files do NOT collect any personally identifiable information, we can not determine who you are or where you live by looking at them.

**Our Listing Services**

If you use any of our web site listing services at our directories, please recognise that **ALL business information** you provide on the submission form can be made publicly available on your special listing page for each site submitted. We also syndicate our listings to other websites (both ours and third-party websites), so you can reasonably expect that your business information will also be displayed on them. If you do not wish your business contact information to be made publicly available, please do not use our services.

As a subscriber to our listing services, you can expect to receive occasional email bulletins from us regarding your use of that service. If you do not want to receive these emails, you can use the unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of each email, or simply reply to the email requesting you be unsubscribed.

**Email Subscriptions**

If you subscribe to any of our services which require submission of your email address, please be assured that your details are kept private. Your details are not sold or rented to any other people. They are used ONLY by us to provide the service requested by you. 

All our email subscriptions go through a **double opt-in process** which confirms you are the actual person requesting the provision of the service. We record all the details including the date/time and IP address associated with that subscription in the event of any complaints.

If you no longer require your subscription, please **use the unsubscribe link included at the bottom of every email** sent to remove yourself from that list, or simply reply to the email requesting you be unsubscribed.

Alternatively send your request to us using the address provided on our contact page

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our sites. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on many of the sites run by Come On Aussie Internet Services. Some of these advertisers may also use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Sydney real estate ads to someone in Sydney, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting the Gold Coast, you may see Gold Coast hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

_AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by[JenSense](http://www.jensense.com/)_
